Deltas Lephalala Front-end Angular Developer



deltaslep@gmail.com +27 659 015 205



linkedin.com/in/deltas-lephalala

Summary

I am a full-stack software engineer with over two years of experience developing and deploying web applications using various technologies. My technical skills include C#, .NET Framework, Angular, MVC, API (SOAP & REST), SQL, Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, Git/& GitHub, Azure DevOps, Microsoft Azure, Blazor, Java, JavaScript/& Typescsrit, Jira, and Linux & Windows OS.

As a software engineer with a strong interest in software engineering, data science, I am passionate about exploring new technologies and finding ways to apply them to solve real-world problems. My technical skills and certifications demonstrate my ability to work on complex projects and my dedication to staying up to date with the latest technologies.

Experience



Full-Stack Software Engineer

LexisNexis

Mar 2022 - Present (14 months+)

- -Work on conveyancing software for Nedbank home loans department
- -Work on Lexis Document Assembly software for Lexis Nexis integral applications, and vendor/and client applications
- -Integrate with internal and external services such as Debicheck, document management, printing, reporting, etc all with different specifications, e.g. SOAP, REST, FTP -Rewrite the existing legacy Windows Forms application in Angular.
- -Swagger REST integration with legacy WCF services
- -NSwag to streamline API integration between front and backend
- -Web authentication for both AD and JWT -Rewrite and redesign legacy UI for web



Software Developer Intern

AOLC | in partnership with MICROSOFT

May 2021 - Feb 2022 (10 months)

Microsoft AppFactory Program - this is a software development internship proffered by Microsoft.

Education



North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, Computer Science and Information **Systems**

2018 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications

- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals Microsoft
- **Û** Linux Mastery: Master the Linux Command Line Udemy
- Angular Fundamentals Simplilearn 3365481
- JavaScript: Introduction Skillsoft
- CAPE Automation Fundamentals Training Percepio®
- in Introduction to Career Skills in Data Analytics LinkedIn
- Introduction to Machine Learning Kaggle
- Python HackerRank
- Python for Data Science IBM
- Data Visualization with Python IBM

Skills

Communication • Time Management • Full-Stack Development • C# • .NET • Angular • HTML5 • CSS • JavaScript/Typescript • SQL • Microsoft SQL Server • MongoDB • Git/GitHub • Bit bucket • Azure Devops • CI&CD • Azure Cloud Computing • VS Code • Visual Studio • Jira • Python

Honors & Awards

Certified Automation Professional (CAP) - Percepio®
Oct 2022

References

Available upon request.